# **TING LUO**

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **Contact**

**Q** 0420750621

Iynn.ting.luo@gmail.com

Greater Melbourne Area

https://github.com/
Lyndating

# **Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- iQuery
- Ruby
- React.js
- Ruby on Rails
- Vue.js
- Python
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- Sinatra
- SQL
- Node.js
- Express/Cors
- Next.js
- Docker
- Coming Soon: AWS

### **PROFILE**

As a highly motivated and proactive developer with passion and a growth mindset, I bring a balance of critical thinking, problem-solving and creativity into life. With 8+ years of experience in customer-facing businesses, I get transferrable skills into my new career.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## General Assembly — Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

- \* Intensive 12-week (500+ hour) full-time software engineering course covering the fundamentals of full-stack software development.
- \* Daily classwork, homework and mini-projects solidify the material learnt.
- \* Developed an online game, "Tic Tac Toe", built from scratch by leveraging HTML, CSS and basic JavaScript functionality.
- \* Full-stack applications: implemented and enhanced multiple relational CRUD operations using Ruby on Rails framework and Postgres database modelling and integrating with third-party APIs (Cloudinary).
- \* Full-stack practical group project "Expense Tracker" experience across various technologies, including HTML/CSS, REACT.js, APIs, Boostrap, Rails PostgresSQL and GitHub.
- \* The final full-stack project, "Shop Now" online shopping website, challenged me to learn more advanced features of React (Redux), Express/Cors, and Firebase Cloud Functions.

#### HVAC Business Admin / Accounts Officer — Jan 2017 - Jan 2022

- \* In charge of all the stock orders, service technicians' daily timesheets and schedules.
- \* Assisting with the SEO team in maintaining WordPress websites.
- \* Methodically led the operation team improving productivity and efficiency.

### Accounting Officer — Jul 2010 - Mar 2015

- \* Managed daily transactions of small business customers on a face-toface basis and maintained healthy relationships with customers
- \* Promoted cross-selling opportunities by referring businesses to appropriate teams

## **EDUCATION**

Macquarie University — Feb 2008 - Jun 2009

Master's degree, Accounting and Finance

University of Adelaide — Feb 2005 - Dec 2007

Bachelor's degree, Accounting